giftsrollup.com 2011-12-25

# Gifts Roll Up

**Sharing Personal Information with Third Parties:**   
We will never sell or give away your personal information to third parties for purposes of building contact lists without your permission. We stand firmly against any transfer of personal information for reasons of building the contact lists of third parties. 

**IP Addresses:**

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our site or web server, and for the general administration of our website. 

**Information Gathering:**

This web site collects online contact information such as email. The information is only used to send your login information, webinar schedules, and or trainng information. This site does not send email promotions.

**Links to Other Sites:**

The Company expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame of content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, via our site you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. the company is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. Please be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of the company and this policy. 

**Children Under 18:**

The Company does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 18 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 18 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. 

If you believe the company has any information from or about anyone under 18, please contact us. 

**Security:**

This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server. 

**Contacting The Company:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us. 

**Policy Changes:**

The Company reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. 

This Privacy Policy was last revised on Oct 5, 2010.
